Wealth. Fame. Power. Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates, obtained this and
everything else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to fire it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dare to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
This is a small seaport village.
For the past year or so, a pirate
ship has been anchored at the port.
A soft wind from the east blows gently
over this peaceful, sleepy place.
Loopy, come on.
What are you doing up there?
I'm not kidding around, you hear me?
I'm really mad!
Watch, I'll prove it to ya!
Yeah, go ahead, kid.
Not sure what you're
planning to do, though.
You idiot!
What'd you do that for?
Alright, drink up! Cheers!
Let's drink to Luffy's courage and
our great journey on the theme!
Cheers!
Didn't hurt at all!
That's a lie if I've ever heard one.
I'm not lying!
And I'm not scared of
getting hurt again, either!
You gotta take me with
you on your next voyage!
I wanna be a pirate like you!
Hahaha!
Yeah, right, as if you
could ever be a pirate.
I don't think you're gonna fare too
well at sea if you sink like an anchor.
I'll be okay as long as
I don't fall overboard!
And besides, I'm a
really good fighter, too!
I've got lots of training!
I mean, when I punch people,
it's like firing a pistol!
A pistol?
If you say so.
Are you makin' fun of me?
Hey!
Don't be in such a sour mood, kiddo!
You're still young!
You should be having fun!
And being a pirate's
more fun than anything!
We get to travel across the endless sea!
Discovering new places all the time!
We're as free as can be!
I'd appreciate it if you clowns
didn't teach him that kind of thing.
But you know it's true, right?
Come on, boss!
We can take him on one little voyage!
What's the harm?
Yeah, he'll be okay!
Fine, but one of you gets left behind.
Yeah, forget that!
Let's get back to drinking!
Put you guys on my side!
I'm just saying, you're much too
young to try and strike out your seed.
You can ask me about it in ten
years and maybe I'll reconsider.
Stupid shakes!
I'm not that little!
Jeez, calm down.
Drink some juice, kid.
Yay, thank you!
Real pirates don't drink juice, big guy!
No, that's not fair!
You tricked me!
Whatever, I'm tired now.
Luffy, you have to try to understand
how the boss feels. Mr. First Mate!
Think about it.
This guy is the captain of a
tough-as-nails pirate crew.
So he knows more than anybody how
dangerous this kind of life can be.
My point is,
he told you not to come along with us
because he didn't want to break your spirit.
You don't get it!
He's just making fun of me
because he thinks I'm a kid!
Hey, Anchor. You see?
You're having fun as always.
Yeah, I get such a kick out of
giving this kid a hard time.
Luffy, would you like
to order some food too?
Put it on my treasure tab, kay?
The treasure tab again?
You know, that does qualify
as stealing. Nuh-uh!
Once I become a pirate and
find a bunch of treasure,
I'm gonna pay back every last bit!
I know you will.
Shanks! Yeah? What?
How much longer are you gonna be here for?
I'm not too sure.
I believe the plan we decided on was to
go on a couple more voyages then head
out towards the north after we're done
with that only a couple more trips huh
okay then i can practice my swimming while
you're here that's a good
idea knock yourself out
excuse us so these are what pass for
pirates here looks awfully sad to me
you see we're mountain bandits
but we didn't come here
to tear your place apart we'll
just take some booze i'm so
sorry sir but we're actually
fresh out of alcohol for the
moment huh those pirates seem
to be drinking though is that
water no that was the last bit
of what i had stuck up well
this is a problem isn't it it
looks like my friends and i
drank the place dry before you
gentlemen came in sorry you
can have this one if you like
it hasn't even been opened yet
how dare you can you not see
who you're talking to you
know damn well that won't
even be enough for a nightcap
oh now the floor's all wet
and sticky look at this
pal i've got a bounty of 8
million berries on my head.
I've killed 56 people, and all of
them were mouthy fools like you.
If I were you, I'd watch my back.
But since we're in the mountains and you're
on the sea, maybe we won't meet again.
Huh?
Sorry about the mess, Machine.
Have you got a rag?
Oh, no, don't worry.
I can take care of it.
Since you like to clean so much, I think
you might find this mess more fulfilling.
Guess I'll see you weaklings another day.
Are you all right, Captain Shanks?
Never been better, Machine.
That Fall really got you good!
Talk about a loser!
Why are you laughing?
You should have stood up to him, Shanks!
That wasn't cool at all!
If you can laugh over something
like that, then you're not a man!
Or a real pirate!
Look, Luffy, I know how you feel, kid.
But all the guy did was
spill a little booze on me.
It's not worth getting so upset about.
Hey, wait a second.
Leave me alone!
You're just a coward!
Why's he stretchy?
Oh no, don't tell me!
What the heck?
It's gone! No way!
Yeah, the Gum-Gum fruit we looted!
It was right in here!
Luffy, tell the truth!
Did you just eat something like this?
Uh, yeah.
It tasted gross, though.
What have you done?
The Gum-Gum fruit is one of
the legendary devil fruits.
It makes your body turn into rubber.
That means you've lost the ability
to swim for the rest of your life!
That can't be!
You idiot!
Hey, Fish Guy, can I have a fishy?
Luffy, it's you!
I heard you missed out on another
big adventure with the pirates.
That's okay.
My body's laid out a rubber now.
This is more fun than going
on a voyage anyway, see?
The crew's been out at
sea for a long time.
Isn't that right, Luffy?
I bet you missed them. No way.
I'm still upset with those guys.
I thought Shanks and his
crew were cool pirates,
but it turns out they're
all totally wimpy.
I don't know.
I think being able to laugh after somebody
humiliates you like those
bandits did is cool,
too.
You don't understand, Monk, you know.
Sometimes a man's gotta
stand up and fight.
You're right.
Maybe I don't get it, huh?
We're back for more.
Looks like those damn
pirates aren't here today.
We were in the neighborhood, so we
thought we'd stop in for a drink.
What's the hold of, honey?
Bring the booze!
Neo, please help!
What's the matter, Machido? It's Luffy!
He's in big trouble!
Let go of him!
Well, this is interesting.
You're gonna pay for that!
This kid is a freak of nature.
See your side for last time, right now!
How much money we could
get if we sold him off?
Fine I don't think I said
anything to offend you personally.
He's a child I don't
intend to fight you and
I'll even pay you to stop
this just let him live.
That's all I ask?
Ah, senior citizen.
Leave it to you to be reasonable.
But you're out of luck.
The rat's already made me angry, so not
even your pitiful prayers can save him now.
Please, no!
That rubber face of yours was
real entertaining for a sec,
but now all I want to do is bash it in.
You guys don't fight fair!
You're scum! Let me go!
Forget selling him.
Let's just kill him.
Luffy!
Have mercy on him, sir!
Nobody was at the port to greet us.
I figured something must be wrong.
The mountain bandits again?
Captain, you're here! Hey, Luffy,
didn't you say before that your punches
were as deadly as getting
shot with a pistol?
Shut up, okay?
You're still in town?
Shove off already.
You'd best leave before
you get hurt take one step
closer and my friend here's
gonna blow your head clean off
Didn't you hear what the man said
do you feel like dying today, buddy?
Well now that you've drawn your pistol
do you plan to actually use it boy?
I'm holding it ain't I what I'm trying to
tell you is the guns
aren't for making threats.
They're made for actions
No way, I don't believe it!
Yeah, these bastards fight dirty!
A little.
Oh, were you expecting saints?
Who the hell do you think
you're dealing with here?
In case it wasn't obvious, you fellows
have picked a fight with a crew of pirates.
Shut your trap!
This ain't about you, so
take your crew and go!
Listen up, bandits.
If I'm sprayed with alcohol or doused
with food, hell, even if I'm spit on,
most of the time I'll
laugh it off and forget it.
But, regardless of what
your reasoning may be,
if you hurt a friend of mine, you
can believe you're gonna pay for it.
Is he for real?
We are, are we?
Go on, fellas.
Show these whips a thing or two.
I'll handle this.
Should be easy.
Don't get too cocky. Stay focused.
If you wanted to fight us, you should have
brought a warship or something bigger.
This is so cool.
Amazing.
No, hold on.
The kid was the one who
attacked us first, all right?
Either way, you're still
a wanted man, aren't you?
A smoke screen.
Come with me!
Luffy!
Aw, crap, I let the bandit take him.
What are we gonna do?
Calm down, boss.
There's no use freaking out over it.
We'll find him in no
time, I swear. Oh, boy.
Can't believe this guy.
Guess I made a clean getaway.
Sorry.
Got no need for you anymore.
See you, Root. Damn it! I suck!
These guys are worthless bandits,
but I still couldn't get one hit in!
I hate this!
It's not fair!
Guys, did you see the
looks on their faces?
All pirates are nothing but
cowards and weaklings. Shut up!
Don't make fun of them like that!
Muffy, no!
Take back what you said
about Shakes and his crew!
Stupid brat.
What the hell?
Help me!
Oh, Jake, you found me!
Get lost!
I'm in your debt, Luffy.
Machine told me about
how you stood up for us,
how you were willing to fight
and put yourself on the line.
Hold on, you can't cry.
You're a man now.
I know, but this is bad.
You lost your arm!
Oh, no need to worry about that.
I've got another one.
I'm just glad you're safe.
Luffy learned many
important things that day.
The harshness of the sea,
his own powerlessness,
and most importantly, the
greatness of a man called Shanks.
That's when young Luffy
resolved with all his heart.
He would become like him.
Jinx!
Are you really about to
leave the village for good?
Uh-huh.
Yep, it's time for us to part ways.
I bet you'll miss me, won't you?
Yeah, but I'm not gonna
beg to come with you,
because I'm gonna become
a pirate all on my own!
That's good, because I wouldn't
bring you with me anyways.
I mean, you'll never make
it as a pirate, kiddo.
We'll too!
Just wait and see!
I'll round up a crew that's
every bit as good as yours!
And we'll find the
world's greatest treasure!
And I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Oh?
Planning to outdo me, are ya?
Okay.
If that's the case, I'll leave this here.
It means more to me than anything.
Give it back someday.
After you become a great pirate.
Okay.
It really does have potential. I know.
He reminds me of myself
back when I was a kid.
Set sail!
One decade later, Luffy's own pirate
adventure began at the very same port.
I can't believe Luffy's finally leaving.
Becoming a pirate is a great
dishonor to our village!
Couldn't ask for a better day for this?
Hey, it's this big guy again.
You shouldn't have done that.
Cause I've been training a
lot over the past 10 years!
PISTOL!
That Outta T .J., you stupid fish!
It's time to get going!
I'm setting out to become
King of the Pirates! We are!
We are!